Contact

Muttath House, Poothole P.O, Thrissur 4 +918156978004 (Mobile) joelhanson2511995@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joel-hanson (LinkedIn)

joel-hanson.github.io (Personal) www.kaggle.com/joelhanson (Other)

Top Skills

Django

Python

Deep Learning

Certifications

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Publications

Deploy API applications to Heroku.

Image Processing Based Plant Leaf Disease Detection

How to make a simple API that generates random name and email using a Flask application.

Joel Hanson

Software Engineer at impress.ai

Thrissur, Kerala, India

Summary

2+ years of experience in python coding and other programming languages like c, c++. On the way of teaching my self to code, I learned Web Development, Database management and some DevOps for the past 2 years. My main focus of learning was always on the backend framework Django. Loves open source contributions a lot, Thus got a chance to contribute to cool projects like carbon.now.sh, snek etc... Currently working in a company called impress.ai which is an Al-powered recruiting solution company.

Experience

impress.ai
Software Engineer
September 2018 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Cochin Area, India

Travidux Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Software Engineer October 2017 - September 2018 (1 year) Chalakudy

Python, Django, Angular.

loku (internship) Web Developer October 2016 - July 2017 (10 months) Karnataka, India

Education

Sahrdaya College Of Engineering And Technology, Kodakara, Thrissur

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science · (2013 - 2017)

St Thomas Thope HSS,Thirssur Higher secondary education, Computer Science · (2011 - 2013)

Don Bosco School Mannuthy SSLC, General Studies · (2005 - 2011)